One meeting. Six million lives.
Conspiracy is a history, drama, war film directed by Frank Pierson.
At the Wannsee Conference on January 20, 1942, senior Nazi officials meet to determine the manner in
which the so-called "Final Solution to the Jewish Question" can be best implemented.
Reinhard Heydrich, played by Kenneth Branagh.
Adolf Eichmann, played by Stanley Tucci.
Dr. Wilhelm Stuckart, played by Colin Firth.
Erich Neumann, played by Jonathan Coy.
Heinrich Müller, played by Brendan Coyle.
Josef Bühler, played by Ben Daniels.
Conspiracy is a 2001 made-for-television drama film that
dramatises the 1942 Wannsee Conference.
Using the authentic script taken from the only surviving transcript recorded during the meeting, the film delves into the
psychology of Nazi officials involved in the "Final Solution of the Jewish question" during World War II.
The film was written by Loring Mandel and directed by Frank Pierson.
Its ensemble cast includes Kenneth Branagh, Stanley
Tucci, Colin Firth and David Threlfall.
Branagh won a Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Lead Actor, and Tucci
was awarded a Golden Globe Award for his supporting role.
The film explores themes of berlin, germany, nazi, war
crimes, holocaust (shoah), world war ii.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.